The start of 2026 for me was probably my
most challenging losing streak I have
had in my trading career. At the start
of the year you have presidents getting
abducted, talks about World War and
these are major news events that are
directly being impacted into the
markets. We're having moves in the
markets that have never happened before
because there are stuff happening in the
world that has never happened before. So
that directly impacted my results in
trading. Now fast forward those two
chaotic months of the year of just
[music] entirely losing week after week,
I'm finally on my first three week
winning streak of the year. I've managed
to make around 150, 160,000 dollars per
week in the last three weeks trading and
in this video I'm going to break down
every single trade and how I managed to
do that. And I want to be very
transparent and be very vulnerable.
Everything in trading is not sunshine
and flowers. You're not going to win
every single week. You're not going to
win every single trade. Even in this
winning streak right now, I managed to
be positive on a winning streak. I'll
show you right now. These are my results
right here. I literally am on a winning
streak and I managed to win and lose the
same amount of trades but ended being
positive. That is the power of the
strategy and the concept that I'm going
to be sharing in this video here with
you guys today. Because trading is
challenging and losing streaks are
inevitable but winning streaks, there's
ways on how to optimize them. So with
that being said, let's get started. Now
before we dive right into on how to
optimize winning streaks and how I
exactly got to this point, I need to
give you guys context on how to face a
losing streak because losing streaks are
inevitable and if you don't know how to
get out of a losing streak, you will
never be able on knowing how to optimize
a winning streak. So the start of the
year for me, since I'm very transparent
with my trading, I post the before, the
during, the after of every single trade
that I take. I just kind of built this
habit in my community and I've really
normalized it in my career to just post
every trade that I take. And I was for
an entire two months losing trade after
trade after trade after trade after
trade.
>> [music]
>> Where I got to the point where everybody
that knows me from social media was
questioning my strategy and questioning
my expertise [music] and my strategy.
And at that point, I realized that some
of these people don't understand the
longevity of trading. And they don't
understand this first rule.
>> [music]
>> And that is that there is no plan B.
There is no changing of a plan. There's
no changing of a strategy [music]
when you're in a losing streak. Losing
streaks are inevitable. You simply just
have to continue to stick to your plan
and trade the best possible trade setup
that you can take. It's almost like if
you were in a rush to go somewhere and
you get stuck into bumper-to-bumper
traffic because sadly there was an
accident in front of you. You can't
reverse. You can't go over the curb. You
can't get out the car and start walking.
You can't run. There's nothing that you
can do other than just stick to the
plan. Stay in your car and continue to
go. You're just going to get there a
little late. Same exact thing here. You
have to stick to your strategy, stick to
your risk management, and you might not
get the profits that you want this week,
but if you stick to the plan, your
risk-reward is positive, you will end up
positive on the long run. Now knowing
that there is no plan B and that there
is no modifying of a strategy if you've
lost three, four trades consecutively,
that there is no modifying risk
management to make back for losses, it's
just sticking to the plan that was
what's going to get you out of that
losing streak. Let me break down exactly
what you need to optimize and keep your
winning streak. So, the most important
thing is going to treat every single
trade the same. Doesn't matter if you
have just lost 10 trades in a row.
Doesn't matter if you have just won 10
trades in a row. Doesn't matter if
you've been break even for the last 10
trades in a row. The next trade has no
correlation to the last trade. It's like
right now if you were to walk into a
restaurant, the type of food and the
type of service that you get at one
restaurant has no correlation to the
restaurant that is right next door to
it. They can be serving completely
different foods, completely different
servers, and completely different
structure. Just because you had a bad
experience at restaurant one doesn't
mean that restaurant two has any
correlation to that. If you enter
restaurant two with a negative mindset
and you are entering with having a
negative expectation, you might find
problems that would have never been a
problem if you had a great experience in
restaurant one. If restaurant one was
great, food was great, when you go to
restaurant two, you might not realize
certain things because of the way that
you approach it. And that's what trading
needs to be like. Doesn't matter if you
just won five trades in a row, you can't
feel like the king of the world and that
you're going to predict the next trade.
If you just lost six trades in a row,
you can't believe that you're now in a
tragic losing streak and you're going to
lose the next trade. Every single trade
is unique and you need to treat it as
cold as you possibly can. Don't have any
association of one trade to the next
trade. That is going to be the core
foundation as to how you stick to your
plan and don't let the last trade avoid
the next trade, for the good or for the
bad. And one of my personal favorites
when it comes to actually optimizing a
winning streak the best that you
possibly can and scaling it
is redefining the trader, not the
strategy. A lot of people, they like to
tighten their stop losses, make their
take profits longer, get better sniper
entries. Not me. I believe for you to
optimize and scale your winning streak
to the max that you possibly can is
enter
the highest possible level as to what
got you into that winning streak and
double down on it. If, for example,
let's say you entered a winning streak
because you traded London session and
New York, which required for you to be
asleep during the duration of the day,
do that. Sleep during the whole entire
day. Sleep during traffic hour, during
the afternoon, so you're just awake
entirely for London and New York
session. If that's what got you into a
winning streak, double down on that.
Don't try and find a way on how to
modify your strategy to not have to stay
awake at those times. If that's what
worked for you, you stick to it. If for
whatever reason what got you to your
winning streak is going to be only
taking trades on the 4-hour timeframe.
Don't find reasons to perfect the 2-hour
or the daily timeframe. Stick to what
you're good at and stay there. Redefine
what got you in your first winning
streak. What got you to the point where
you are and just double down on it.
Don't fix something that's not broken or
don't try and find something else if you
haven't maximized the potential of
what's right in front of you right now.
And to add to the last key of the entire
operation of having the correct mindset
and approach to sticking to a winning
streak is not letting your ego get to
you. Ego is probably the thing that
holds traders back the most because when
traders lose, they don't want to accept
that it was their mistake. They try and
find whatever external reason as to why
something went wrong and they don't
realize that it was them. And also an
ego when you believe you know everything
and despite you still maybe having some
losses and maybe having some wins, your
ego gets the best of you. You can't
embrace that you're still a student of
the markets and that you don't know
everything and that you will forever be
a student of the markets at whatever
level that you are and you can't move
further than what you already are
because you aren't ready to accept that
you're wrong and then simply
enter new change into whatever mistakes
you're making in your trading so you can
continue to grow as a trader, not just
stay stuck because you want to be right
about whatever it is that you're wrong
about in your trading. So, I've seen
traders come and go all the time where
they just don't want to accept that
they're wrong. Their ego gets to them
and they entirely just throw their
profits down the drain. They throw
entirely their time down the drain. And
I've also seen egos ruin people. They're
on top of the world, they're making the
most amount of money, they're having
their first winning streak, their first
winning month, first winning year and
then a situation like what happened to
me at the beginning of this year happens
to them. And then what ends up happening
is they don't know how to manage and
contain that because they're so high on
their horse that they fall very hard
because they weren't prepared for that
and they just can't accept that they
have to potentially modify something if
they're making changes that they
shouldn't be making. So, with that being
said, let's get into the technicals and
the actual trades that led me to be in a
winning streak in these last 3 weeks.
Let's break them down. All right, now
diving into the markets, we're going to
break down the first out of the four
trades out of my winning streak for the
last 3 weeks, which is going to be
GBPNZD. Just pop it up, editor. It's
literally the first trade. We made
$269,000
on this first position. So, this
position was a counter trend trade. So,
as you guys can see right here, this is
the position that we entered at this
point. And it might look like a great
trade from here. It might look like very
clean structure. You can tell that this
market is creating lower highs, lower
lows, lower highs, lower lows. Then we
shifted to creating highs and lows. So,
at this point right here, if I were to
just take this market structure
>> [music]
>> that I have just drawn up right here,
just move it to the right. We're just
going to It's literally this exact same
structure. Move it up here so it's a bit
more visual. As you guys can see,
literally the entire market was creating
lower highs and lower lows being
bearish. Inverted head and shoulders
right here. We broke, retested that
neckline, created new higher high,
higher low, and then we retested that
structure point. This is the most
classic break and retest trend
continuation pattern that you can
possibly see. So, the daily time frame
was bullish. Now, the reason why I call
this a counter trend trade is because at
the time of me entering this trade, the
weekly time frame is very bearish. You
can see here this is a higher high,
higher low, higher high structure, lower
low. So, this market was bearish at the
time of me entering this position. You
guys can see right here, this market was
bearish.
This was the higher low. This was the
higher high, and then we shifted to the
downside. Now,
the reason why I entered this trade is
because I believed this weekly time
frame from here we could have had a very
deep retracement into here to then head
to the downside.
>> [music]
>> So, I was interested in entering this
counter trend trade retracement, but I
needed the daily and the 4-hour to align
with that. So, that's where I go down
here on the So, the weekly time frame we
identify that it's overdue that
retracement. We're above the EMA daily
time frame, we shifted bullish, so I buy
there on the daily.
>> [music]
>> And then when I go down to the 4-hour
time frame, 4-hour time frame, at the
time of me entering this position
[music] was bullish. So, the market
structure shifted bullish, and then we
simply continued to the upside. My stop
loss was very [music] conservative. It
was below this area of interest, below
the daily structure point, and I had a
simple 1:2 [music]
risk-to-reward. This is a beautiful
trade. Now, the reason why I got out at
this area right here is because I
believed
that the weekly could have a reaction
from here. Because remember, the weekly
time frame [music] is bearish. So, I'm
taking a counter trend trade with the
4-hour and daily to that weekly area of
interest from where the weekly time
frame could have a reaction. So, think
about [music] it like this. The weekly
time frame is having this move like
this. Let me delete this.
The weekly time frame is having a move
like this.
Right? So, this is where price on this
retracement is where I'm [music]
interested in capitalizing off of this
retracement because if we make it to
this resistance, clearly whenever we're
below we head [music] down, we head
[clears throat] down. When we're above
we head up. So, as of right now when I
was taking this trade way over here,
we're very far from there. So, I can
take [music] the trade to that area
right there. So, this is what I waited
for the daily time frame [music]
to shift bearish. This is where you see
the bearish, the head and shoulders, and
it shift bullish. So, I entered on the
daily time frame shifting bullish
because it was creating that retracement
for the weekly time frame to head
[music] to the upside. So, that was that
shift right here. If I go down to the
daily time frame, it's the exact same
shift. I'm literally seeing the market
go from being bearish to being bullish.
And that's where we entered, right on
that retest right there. I waited for
that candlestick to close so I can have
that confirmation in order for me to
enter this trade to head to the upside.
So, I waited about 5 days for this trade
to hit my take profit, stayed very
patient, and we made it there.
Now, I don't care that this trade went
past my take profit. I wasn't looking to
maximize this to the last pip. To me, it
made sense for this market to simply
have a reaction from this area and then
now supposedly head to the downside. The
fact that it kept going up, it is what
it is. It's part of the process. I'm not
going to change the plan. Not going to
think that I did something wrong or
modify it to optimize it to the last
pip. My trade was a counter trend trade.
It was already aggressive. It was meant
to be a 1:2. I simply move on to the
next one. So, this is the first trade
which led us to have our first solid
win. And it was a beauty of a trade.
Now, my next trade is NZD/CAD as a loss.
So, I took a $161,000
loss. As you can see from the other
losses and wins, my wins will always
outweigh my losses. So, NZD/CAD, I ended
up losing this position. And when I lost
it, I was pretty much straight into stop
loss. And I was totally okay with it
because I had already pre-calculated my
risk. So, NZD/CAD, this is the loss that
I took over here. It was a bit of a
higher risk trade because we are below
this resistance level here, this
resistance and support. So, weekly time
frame, as you can tell, whenever we're
above, we're heading up. Whenever we're
above, we're heading up. When I was
buying over here, technically we were
below it. So, that was already the first
wrong thing that I did. I was just okay
with it at the time. The daily time
frame gave me a decent structure, but I
really was mainly entering this trade
just off of the 4-hour. I saw some
accumulation at this area right here. I
liked that on the 4-hour we were above
this area of interest, but it was a
choppy market overall. I should have
stayed away, but I was uh totally okay
with the risk and uh I simply took the
trade and went straight to stop loss. My
stop loss was at an area, if it got hit,
I would have been entirely wrong, and
that's exactly what happened. Price hit
my stop loss, came back to retest the
area below, and then just [music] kept
heading to the downside. Obviously, now
you fast forward a bit more time and it
did have a push to the upside, but it is
what it is. It's just a loss. The next
trade is a GBP/CAD, where we lost $195.
So, again, I have a winning streak, but
I am taking losses. It [music] is part
of the process. You could be in a
winning streak and taking losses as long
as your wins outweigh your losses.
GBP/CAD, I literally had a perfect setup
present itself because this was a
beautiful weekly area of interest, as
you can tell here. The weekly time frame
was bearish, lower high, lower low.
We're coming back to retest this area of
interest right here, support, [music]
support, support. At the time of me
looking at this position, this is what
This is literally what I'm seeing right
here. I'm seeing [music] a beautiful
weekly break and retest, rejecting the
EMA, rejecting previous structure.
[music]
Daily time frame is showing massive
accumulation at this area. Whenever
we're above, we head up. Whenever we're
below, we head [music] down. We're below
the EMA.
4-hour time frame is giving me a clean
head and shoulders. You guys know that's
one of my favorite patterns. [music] And
I simply place my stop loss above the
area where if it gets hit, it should
break above it.
>> [music]
>> And once it breaks above it, it should
continue going in this direction. I like
placing my stop losses at an area where
if it gets hit, I'm entirely wrong. I'm
not trying to have the tightest stop
loss. I'm trying to have a stop loss put
at an area where it's very difficult for
the market to hit it if I'm right about
the trade. So,
I enter my position.
As soon as I enter it, pretty much just
goes straight into stop loss and does
exactly as I said, goes above the area,
retests it, and then it [music] just
continues heading to the upside. So,
these are the type of losses that I
don't mind to take at all because I'm
entirely wrong about the direction and
that is totally fine. And then last but
not least, we have EUR AUD, which is my
bigger trade, which I should have
actually taken a much larger take profit
on this because I was
entirely right about this trade for a
very long time and I could have
maximized so much This This could have
literally been my biggest trade that
I've ever taken, but I simply didn't.
So, this is EUR AUD here. This is where
I entered the position. Very clean
trade.
At the time of me taking this trade, the
daily time frame was bullish. So, this
market had created a clean high. So,
whenever you see a market like this,
right? Let me Let me give you guys an
example of what I did here, all right?
Whenever you see a market do something
like this, all right? Give clean bearish
structure to the downside and then we
have a massive shift like this, what I
anticipate is for the market to have a
retracement to then continue heading to
the upside. So, I saw an opportunity in
taking a trade in this countertrend
pullback right here. So, if you notice,
that's exactly what happened here. This
is the bearish market. Lower highs and
lower lows, all right? We just slightly
adjust this right here. Very clean
structure. It's literally all the same
thing.
And we have the big push up. So, after
the big push up, we approach this
resistance. After it's approaching this
resistance, it accumulates for about 5
days. Lots of rejections, rejections
from the EMA, and then that's when I go
down to the lower time frame. I'm like,
"Okay, if the lower time frame shows me
that it's going to start shifting
because obviously the 4-hour time frame
has a lot of structure in here. And if
the 4-hour time frame starts shifting,
that's going to be my indication that
this is going to head to the downside."
That's where I go down to the 4-hour.
And at that high, at this resistance,
the 4-hour creates a beautiful head and
shoulders time frame head and shoulders
pattern. Left head, right shoulder,
broke and retested that neckline.
Beautiful counter trend trade. And I
ended up closing here at a 1:2. If I
would have continued to hold this
position all the way down here, I would
have gotten nearly a 1:6.
Would have been a million dollar trade.
But, guess what? I don't dwell on it. I
don't let this trade affect my next
trade. I stuck to my plan. I was okay
with having a 1:2 risk to reward, and I
didn't let that affect my next trade. I
mean, you know what? I missed out on an
extra 3% on this trade. The next one,
I'm going to maximize it to a 1:5.
Again, the next trade has no association
to the last trade. The last trade could
hit your 1:2 to the dot and then reverse
all the way back to stop loss. You can't
have this generic I'm sorry, you can't
have this biased approach based off of
what happened on your last trade to what
you're going to do in your next trade.
My plan is always the same. Get out at a
1:2. If you're at a 1:2 and it makes
sense to continue to hold, you do that
then. At the time of me entering this
trade, it made no sense to continue to
hold [music]
because again, this was supposed to have
a reaction from this area. I saw this as
the area of [music] interest where the
market could have a push and head to the
upside. I saw this as the area where the
market could have its shift, right? It
could have its support here and then
head to the upside. It simply [music]
didn't do that and it just continued
heading to the downside. Obviously, we
can't predict the future. If not, I
would be a gazillionaire. But, this
market simply decided [music] to
continue to have the push to the
downside. And at least I was right about
this part of the move. So, have you
noticed there's a consistent approach
when it comes to my stop losses, a
consistent approach when it comes to my
take profit, there's a consistent
approach when it comes to the actual
trade management because I am sticking
to my plan and I am closing at my 1:2
risk to reward. I am not letting the
last trade affect the next trade. It's
all sticking to the plan. And most
importantly, quality over quantity. It's
been 3 weeks and I've taken four trades.
Quality over quantity. And a lot of
people don't really understand what to
do when they win a trade. Some people
almost question themselves, what now?
And I'm like, well, just keep doing what
you were doing. The whole reason as to
why you're trading with a strategy, as
to why you're doing top-down analysis,
as to why you're even involved in the
markets, it's to make [music] money. So,
when you make money, you can't be
surprised. And
when you lose, you can't be surprised
either. That's the whole reason why you
place a stop loss and why you
pre-calculate your risk. So, nothing
[music] is random. Everything is
pre-calculated. The problem is that
people get lost in the process and they
try and extract money from the markets.
And the money will follow if you have a
proper plan. So, if you lose money, you
can't be surprised because you
pre-calculated your risk. And if you win
money, you can't be surprised because
that's the whole reason why you took the
trade in the first place. That's why
you're here doing the analysis. And some
people forget this in their journey of
being a trader. That's why every single
week when I host a call with my students
where I share with them the top markets
that I am interested in. Not only do I
give them the top markets that I'm
trading for the week, why I'm interested
in trading, why we should avoid other
markets, I refresh their mind as to why
they need to stick to quality over
quantity and why it's okay to lose.
[music]
And we review their trades to make sure
that they're doing the right thing from
the wrong thing. You're part of a
community where you are engaging with
other traders having the same direction
and the same goals as you. So, it's a
lot easier for students to succeed when
they have this type of guidance every
single week. So, if you guys want to
become a student and want to know more
about it, hit the link in the
description down below. And hopefully we
can take this winning streak that you
guys [music] have seen here today to 10
weeks, 20 weeks, 25 weeks and break my
personal record of 14 weeks. It's the
longest I've ever had it. I think the
closest I got was about 8 weeks and I
lost it. So, hopefully we can break that
this [music] year. And I hope you guys
enjoyed this video. And let's see what
the next couple of weeks have for store
for us. If you guys like this video, hit
that like and subscribe button. I'll see
you guys in the next one.